instafinder.com 2010-11-12

# InstaFinder Search Portal

Information We Gather  
We do not purposefully collect any personally identifiable information about you (such as your name, address, email address, or telephone number). Our Instafinder pages, or any software used to obtain such Instafinder pages, may, however, transmit limited non-personally identifiable information, such as your IP address, type of browser and operating system, unique software ID, version of the Broadspring software, internal software status indicators (including error codes to determine if the software has encountered any internal errors), a tag that identifies any Broadspring, Inc distribution partner from whom you may have downloaded or installed the software, and keyword and error search queries entered in your browser if you are using our software known as 'Instafinder.' Please note that any search query information collected by us is maintained by Broadspring on an aggregated basis ( i.e., together with the queries of all of our end-users) for the purposes of generating statistics regarding the use of our software or services (such as the number of queries performed by the average end-user per month, a list of the most popular query terms, etc.), and is never used in a manner that matches specific search query information with any particular end-user. To properly reflect your language, filtering and other preferences, our Instafinder pages may also use cookies ( i.e. packets of information containing your preferences that are sent to your browser and sent back by your browser each time your browser accesses our server). Cookies that we may use may only be read by the server that placed them there. If you wish to control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your browser, you should refer to the documentation accompanying your browser.

How We Use the Information We Gather  
Most of the limited, non-personally identifiable information collected is used to provide more relevant products and services to our end-users. For example, Broadspring may use your IP address to determine which language to use to provide you with Internet search results. In addition, information collected from end-users may be used in aggregate form to, among other things, determine the total number of distributed and active copies of our software or total number of end-users who are using our services, prepare utilization reports for our partners or affiliates (collectively, 'Partners'), diagnose and fix compatibility problems or other bugs in our software, and perform statistical analyses to enable Broadspring to build higher quality, more useful online services. The information collected from end-users also allows Broadspring to determine if the software on an end-user's computer is encountering internal errors or needs to be updated and permits Broadspring to deliver search results pages that are as responsive as possible to an individual end-user's particular search query (e.g., serves results in the end-user's native language and tailored to the end-user's country of connectivity).

When We Disclose the Information We Gather  
As a general rule, we do not share the information we collect from end-users with third-parties. However, search terms or phrases inputted as queries by our end-users are transmitted to certain Partners with whom Broadspring has subcontracted (such as Google, Overture Services, FindWhat.com and others) to obtain Internet search results or other services in response to such search queries. In addition, some of the information we collect is provided, in aggregate form only, to our Partners solely for purposes related to our relationships with such Partners, not for the purposes of marketing to our end-users. While we encourage our Partners to adhere to our Privacy Policy, we are not responsible for their actions or omissions, including the manner in which they use information that they receive from Broadspring or that they independently may collect from you. If in the future we sell or transfer assets or portions of our business, or if we experience a change in control, reorganization or liquidation, we may transfer such information to our successor or buyer, subject to this Privacy Policy. Finally, we reserve the right to disclose any information about you if you violate any of our published guidelines, or as required by law, or to defend our rights or the rights and well-being of our other end-users, or if you are involved (or are reasonably suspected to be involved) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order.

No Responsibility for Third-Party Practices  
Any websites displayed to you when you click on a link or advertisement on an Instafinder web page have been developed by third-parties over which Broadspring exercises no control. Such websites may send their own cookies to end-users, collect data, or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Broadspring is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, including such websites use of any information collected when Broadspring end-users are directed to or click through to such websites. Even though such information might not identify you personally, we strongly encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of those websites.
